(cheering)
("Personality Crisis" by New York Dolls)
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ No-no-no-no, no-no-no ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ We can't take her this week ♪
♪ And her friends don't
want another speech ♪
♪ Hoping for a better day ♪
♪ To hear what she's gotta say ♪
♪ All about that personality crisis ♪
♪ You got it while it was hot ♪
♪ But frustration, heartache,
that's what ya got ♪
♪ I gotta say about the personality ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Now you're tryna be something ♪
♪ Now you gotta do something ♪
♪ Wanna be someone who counts ♪
♪ But you're thinkin'
'bout the times you did ♪
♪ They took every ounce ♪
♪ Well, it sure got to be a shame ♪
♪ When you start to scream and shout ♪
♪ You gotta contradict all the times ♪
♪ You're butterflyin' about ♪
♪ You was butterflyin' ♪
♪ About a personality crisis ♪
♪ You got it while it was hot ♪
♪ It's always hot, you
know it's frustration ♪
♪ Heartache, that's what ya got ♪
♪ I gotta shout about your personality ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
(cheering)
♪ And you're a prima ballerina
on a spring afternoon ♪
♪ Change on into the Wolfman ♪
♪ You're howlin' at the moon (howls) ♪
♪ Personality crisis ♪
♪ You got it while it was hot ♪
♪ It's always hot, you
know it's frustration ♪
♪ Heartache, that's what ya got ♪
♪ The personality ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, ah ♪
♪ Now with all the crossin'
fingers that Mother Nature sends ♪
♪ Your mirror's getting jammed
up with all your friends ♪
♪ This personality, everything
is starting to blend ♪
♪ Uh-Uh, not like one ♪
♪ Personality, when your
mind starts to blend ♪
♪ Got so much personality ♪
♪ Impression of a friend of a friend ♪
♪ Of a friend of a friend of a friend ♪
♪ Personality, wonderin'
how celebrities ever mend ♪
♪ Lookin' fine on television ♪
♪ Personality crisis ♪
♪ You got it while it was hot ♪
♪ It's always hot, you
know it's frustration ♪
♪ Heartache, that's all ya got ♪
♪ Oh, don't you worry ♪
♪ Personality crisis ♪
♪ Please don't cry ♪
♪ It's just a personality crisis ♪
♪ Please don't stop ♪
♪ Because you walk a personality ♪
♪ Talk a personality ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
(cheering)
- [Announcer] Next on Don Hershman's.